Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
Princeton Football Films Collection
1935-2012
1935-1990
University Archives
Princeton University. Athletics Department.
AC297
1 box
2858 items
Princeton University was a participant in the first intercollegiate football game in America in 1869. Since then, the University has maintained a varsity football team, competing each season against other colleges in the Ivy League Athletic Conference, including traditional rival Yale. The collection consists of film reels documenting Princeton varsity football games between 1935 and 1990, as well as video of the 2012 season.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
For preservation reasons, original analog and digital media may not be read or played back in the reading room. Users may visually inspect physical media but may not remove it from its enclosure. All analog audiovisual media must be digitized to preservation-quality standards prior to use. Audiovisual digitization requests are processed by an approved third-party vendor. Please note, the transfer time required can be as little as several weeks to as long as several months and there may be financial costs associated with the process. Requests should be directed through the Ask Us Form.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of film reels amd video documenting Princeton varsity football games between 1935 and 2012. Series 1 contains original film reels (1935-1990), stored offsite at the ReCAP facility. Series 2 contains video footage of the 2012 varsity football season.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research use.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
The film reels are stored offsite at the ReCAP facility. Most of the film is 16mm or 8mm and has not been transferred to any other format. Early films are fragile and have significant warping, along with other potential preservation issues.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Complete information on the acquisition of the collection is not available. At least some of the football films were transferred from the Princeton University Athletics Department. The 2012 videos were transferred from the Athletics Department in 2012 (AR.2012.146).
Appraisal
No materials have been separated from the collection.
Accruals
Periodic accruals to the collection may occur.
Related Materials
Additional Princeton football films, especially season highlight reels, can be found in AC047, Historical Audiovisual Collection.
Recordings of lightweight football games can be found in AC310, Sprint Football VHS Tapes Collection.
Programs for many of the games recorded in this collection can be found in Series 2 of AC206, Office of Athletic Communications Records.
Princeton University. Athletics Department.
Biographical / Historical
Princeton University was a participant in the first intercollegiate football game in America in 1869. Since then, the University has maintained a varsity football team, competing each season against other colleges in the Ivy League Athletic Conference, including traditional rival Yale.
Football films.; Films.; Princeton University. Football.
- Princeton Football Film Reels, 1935-1990; 2187 items
  Arrangement
  In chronological order. No arrangement action taken or arrangement information not recorded at the time of processing.
  Scope and Contents
  Series 1 contains original film reels (mostly 16 mm or 8 mm) documenting Princeton varsity football games between 1935 and 1990. For many games more than one reel exists, documenting only offense or defensive plays, practices or scrimmages, kicking, or specific quarters of the game. Duplicate prints of certain reels are also included in the collection.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Most of the film is 16mm or 8mm and has not been transferred to any other format. Early films are fragile and have significant warping, along with other potential preservation issues. Access follows Mudd Manuscript Library policy for preservation and access to audiovisual materials.
  - 1935-1939, 20 items
    - 1935 Navy (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1935 Navy (Full Game))
    - 1935 Navy (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1935 Navy (Full Game))
    - 1935 Rutgers (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1935 Rutgers (Full Game))
    - 1936 Cornell (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1936 Cornell (Full Game))
    - 1936 Dartmouth (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1936 Dartmouth (Full Game))
    - 1936 Harvard (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1936 Harvard (Full Game))
    - 1936 Penn (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1936 Penn (Full Game))
    - 1936 Rutgers (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1936 Rutgers (Full Game))
    - 1937 Chicago (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Chicago (Full Game))
    - 1937 Cornell (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Cornell (Full Game))
    - 1937 Dartmouth (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Dartmouth (Full Game))
    - 1937 Harvard (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Harvard (Full Game))
    - 1937 Navy (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Navy (Full Game))
    - 1937 Rutgers (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Rutgers (Full Game))
    - 1937 Unknown (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Unknown (Full Game))
    - 1937 Virginia (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Virginia (Full Game))
    - 1937 Yale (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1937 Yale (Full Game))
    - 1938 Penn (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1938 Penn (Full Game))
    - 1938 Yale (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1938 Yale (Full Game))
    - 1939 Williams (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1939 Williams (Full Game))
  - 1940-1948, 42 items
    - 1940 Army (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1940 Army (Full Game))
    - 1940 Dartmouth (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1940 Dartmouth (Full Game))
    - 1940 Rutgers (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1940 Rutgers (Full Game))
    - 1940 Yale (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1940 Yale (Full Game))
    - 1941 Columbia (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1941 Columbia (Full Game))
    - 1941 Navy (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1941 Navy (Full Game))
    - 1941 Yale (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1941 Yale (Full Game))
    - 1942 Army (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1942 Army (Full Game))
    - 1942 Brown (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1942 Brown (Full Game))
    - 1942 Dartmouth (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1942 Dartmouth (Full Game))
    - 1942 Lakehurst (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1942 Lakehurst (Full Game))
    - 1942 Penn (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1942 Penn (Full Game))
    - 1942 Yale (Full Game), 1 item (Item 1942 Yale (Full Game))
    - 1946 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1946 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1946 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1946 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1946 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1946 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1946 Brown (Full Game 5), 1 item (Item 1946 Brown (Full Game 5))
    - 1946 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1946 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1946 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1946 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1946 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1947 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1947 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1947 Harvard (full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1947 Harvard (full Game 1))
    - 1947 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1947 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1947 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1947 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1947 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1947 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1947 Lafayette (Practice/Scrimage 1), 1 item (Item 1947 Lafayette (Practice/Scrimage 1))
    - 1947 Lafayette (Practice/Scrimage 2), 1 item (Item 1947 Lafayette (Practice/Scrimage 2))
    - 1947 Lafayette (Practice/Scrimage 3), 1 item (Item 1947 Lafayette (Practice/Scrimage 3))
    - 1947 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1947 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1947 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1947 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1947 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1947 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1948 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1948 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1948 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1948 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1948 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1948 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1948 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1948 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1948 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1948 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1948 Virginia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1948 Virginia (Full Game 1))
    - 1948 Virginia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1948 Virginia (Full Game 2))
    - 1948 Virginia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1948 Virginia (Full Game 3))
  - 1951-1959, 61 items
    - 1951 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1951 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1951 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1951 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1951 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1951 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1952 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 1))
    - 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 2))
    - 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 3))
    - 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1952 Lafayette (Full Game 4))
    - 1952 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1952 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1952 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1952 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1952 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1952 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1952 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1952 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1952 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1952 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1952 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1952 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1952 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1952 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1953 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1953 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1953 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1953 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1953 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1953 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1953 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1953 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 1), 1 item (Item 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 1))
    - 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 2), 1 item (Item 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 2))
    - 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 3), 1 item (Item 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 3))
    - 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 4), 1 item (Item 1953 Fordham (Practice/Scrimage 4))
    - 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1953 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1954 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1954 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1954 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1954 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1954 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1954 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1954 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1954 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1954 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1954 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1954 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1954 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1954 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1954 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1954 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1954 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1954 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1954 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1954 Yale (full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (full Game 4))
    - 1954 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1954 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1955 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1956 Auburn (Special), 1 item (Item 1956 Auburn (Special))
    - 1956 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1956 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1956 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1956 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1957 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1957 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1957 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1957 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1957 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1957 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1959 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1959 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1959 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1959 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1959 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1959 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1959 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1959 Harvard (Full Game 3))
  - 1960-1967, 102 items
    - 1960 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1960 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1960 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1960 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1961 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1961 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1961 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1961 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1963 Brown (Offense), 1 item (Item 1963 Brown (Offense))
    - 1963 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1963 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1963 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1963 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1963 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1963 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1963 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1963 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1963 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1963 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1963 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1963 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1963 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1963 None (practice/Scrimage 2), 1 item (Item 1963 None (practice/Scrimage 2))
    - 1963 None (Practice/Scrimage 4), 1 item (Item 1963 None (Practice/Scrimage 4))
    - 1963 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1963 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1963 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1963 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1963 Penn (full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1963 Penn (full Game 3))
    - 1963 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1963 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1963 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1964 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1964 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1964 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1964 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1964 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1964 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1964 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1964 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 2))
    - 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 3))
    - 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 4))
    - 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 5), 1 item (Item 1964 Lehigh (Full Game 5))
    - 1964 None (Miscellaneous), 1 item (Item 1964 None (Miscellaneous))
    - 1965 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1965 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1965 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1965 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1965 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1965 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1965 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1965 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1965 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1965 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1965 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1965 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1965 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1965 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1965 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1965 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1965 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1965 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1965 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1965 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1965 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1965 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1965 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1965 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1965 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1966 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1966 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1966 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1966 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1966 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1966 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1966 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1966 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1966 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1966 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1966 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1966 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1966 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1966 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1966 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1966 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1966 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1966 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1966 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1966 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1966 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1966 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1967 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1967 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1967 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1967 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1967 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1967 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1967 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1967 Yale (Full Game 4))
  - 1968-1969, 73 items
    - 1968 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1968 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1968 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1968 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1968 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1968 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1968 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Rutgers (Full Game 4))
    - 1968 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1968 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1968 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1968 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1968 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1968 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1968 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1968 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1969 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1969 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1969 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1969 Colgate (Defense2), 1 item (Item 1969 Colgate (Defense2))
    - 1969 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1969 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1969 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1969 Colgate (Offense 2))